

LEO GARDBERG

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

- +46 70 497 1022
- Leo.gardberg@gmail.com
- https://leoxd19.github.io/
- Stockholm / Uppsala (SWEDEN)

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Committed computer science student with international experience and a passion for innovation and problem-solving. Dedicated to leveraging programming and technology to tackle modern challenges, including climate change. Inspired by a love for nature, creativity, and a perspective enriched by the arts and philosophy.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

SIGTUNASKOLAN HUMANISTISKA LÄROVERKET (SSHL)

UPPSALA UNIVERSITY

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA NATURAL SCIENCE (ENG)

B.SC. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

2015-2018

2022-PRESENT

CAREER HISTORY

PLÅT PELLES CAFÉ

May 2018 - Aug 2018 **BARISTA & SERVER**

SIGTUNAHÖJDEN HOTEL & **CONFERENCE**

SERVICE STAFF & BARTENDER

Aug 2018 - Oct 2019

CORE SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, SQL, Ruby
- Frameworks & Tools: Node.js, Flask, Git, Matplotlib
- Specialized Knowledge: Full Stack Development (JavaScript), Data Analysis (Excel: pivot tables, visualization, automation)
- LANGUAGES: Swedish: Native. English: Fluent.

LANDSCAPE ASSISTANT & IT SUPPORT

WOOD PROPERTIES

Feb 2019 - Jul 2019

COMPLETED COURSES & MISC

- Al & Philosophy
- Programming Techniques
- Fundamental Information Systems
- Entrepreneurial Agreements & Responsibilities
- Administration 1
- Swedish drivers licence
- PADI Certified Deep Water Diver